I thought it was blue, blue, blue, blue, and if it had been purple or something, I would have done it.
I'm not a quitter.
You mean you didn't like it?
I wondered how long I would be an idol.
I wondered how long I could do this dance.
But not so much Ichi and Neyo.
I'm still waiting for my senpai to come back.
Next episode
Oh, I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous.
What are we going to talk about?
Are you guys nervous?
Shyness?
I'm so nervous.
I felt like that a lot.
I felt it a lot while I was doing my makeup.
What was that about?
I don't know.
You mean you had a bad feeling about it?
No, not like that.
I felt calm.
I'm really nervous.
I've never been involved with Japanese idols before.
You are not nervous?
I am very nervous. Me too.
I'm not nervous at all.
You don't seem to be able to push my attention.
I'm the type of person who doesn't push too hard.
So I'll do my best. You've never met me before, right? Probably the two of you. Yes, that's right. Do you two have business cards?
We do, don't we? Yes, we do. We had a chance to work together once at the Fukuoka concert, and we both wore blue, and since we were both in charge of blue, we took two shots.
I also wear this color, and I saw it on Twitter. I thought my hair was blue.
I used to have blue hair, but it fell a lot, and since I do YouTube, blue is the color for that. Oh, so everyone's hair is blue. That's right. We had one thing in common.
Did you plan it? He was planning it.
So what do we do now? Who should we start with?
Shall we go?
Shall we go? Please.
I'll go.
My weapon that other idols can't beat.
Weapon?
I think my weapon is my refusal to give up.
I'll tell you why.
I was AKB48 until I became AKB.
I know, I know, I know.
I know this.
I forgot.
And before I joined AKB, I had to go through the 4th audition.
And from there, for 11 years, I was not selected for the rest of my life.
It's been 11 years since I auditioned for AKB, and it took 11 years for me to finally get selected.
She is not a good quitter.
So we were talking about how being bad at giving up is also one of her strengths.
But isn't that very important in the idol business?
So, I asked him if it was a lot of effort.
I think it's not so bad that you didn't give up.
Don't you get asked that question a lot? What is good? What is your strength? I do a lot of live performances, and I'm always asked what I like about my fans.
I do a lot of live performances, and I think I'm pretty good at talking to my fans there.
I get responses from the audience that I know are mine.
Like pointing at me or waving until I wave back.
That definitely makes me happy.
When you respond, can you focus on those with blue penlights?
Priority.
Priority. I'd definitely be happy.
If people want it, they can get that blue stuff. Like, love and wear it.
I'll wear it. I can get that many lessons. I'm sure of it. Because they will notice. Yes, it is. I'm excited.
Do you guys do any fan-surfing? I'm pretty fan-focused myself.
Me too. I've got another one. I'm going to follow it today.
There are a lot of AKBs in Japan.
I use it. Heavenly light. Oh, I see. Like red and white.
I'm blue and purple, so I watch the blue and purple people for the rest of my life, but when there are so many people, there is a lot of overlap,
So, I noticed that the person I kept looking at all the way through the show had one of the lights of a different person at the end.
It happens. But I only saw those people.
Two colors seem to be very difficult. Even one color can look blue-purple depending on the color of the lighting.
So I think blue, blue, blue, and if it was purple, I would deflect it like this.
It's like that. It's very awkward.
It's so awkward.
But I'm also a very focused person, and I've already seen blue.
I respond to those who are right for me. Also, when the battery is about to run out, the color gradually fades away.
If it's too short, it won't work anymore. I'm really curious about which is which. It's a common thing, isn't it?
Which is it? There are many times when I wonder if it's one or the other.
Or there are people who look at me a lot. Sometimes. Even if they don't have it. That's right, I don't have it. But those people were probably looking at me. I wonder how they feel.
But they were interested. I thought they were looking at me because they thought I was cute, but I guess not. It's good to see someone with a straight face sometimes. It's kind of amazing.
It makes me fluffy. Are you the only one with your own color?I get fluffy. Are you the only one with your own color?
Just me. It's so nice. I'm jealous. How many colors are there?
I don't know, it could be anything. Some of the girls are saying rainbow colors. It's hard to have rainbow colors, isn't it?
There are kids who say rainbow colors. It could be anything. Is it a coincidence that I saw two of them today? Or is it blue because it's your costume?
Yes, they are blue because they are in their own costumes. I don't have that kind of thing, so I thought it was nice. But AKB members are all the same. The color and so on. But we have a uniformity and I think it's really cute.
I should have chosen the blue one. Do you have blue ones? They are all blue.
Baba Bambi was my first idol group. We went from five to seven members, so I had never experienced a large group, and I wondered what it would be like.
I couldn't imagine performing with 16 or 15 members at all.
When choreographing, if it was a fairly small group, would you have to choreograph while doing the formation, or would you have to memorize the choreography first?
If the chorus was the same, I would memorize the chorus first, and then wait for this side of the chorus to start,
It is not uncommon to find kids who can already do 16 positions on the same song,
There were many who had already done all the positions,
It's super hard work, isn't it?
Sixteen positions? For singles, anyone can do more than 5 or 6 positions.
Wow!
I can't do it. I can't do it. I don't forget everything after a year. After the single period is over, I won't remember anything else. So when I really remember, it's like a mixture of this and that. Wow!
And I wondered how long I would be an idol. I was wondering how long I would be an idol. I wonder if I am deciding how long I will stay as an idol because I am young.
How much will I be asked to do? Of course I would like to continue if I am asked to do something, but I don't have a clear vision of what I want to do and when I want to do it.
But I do wonder how long I will be able to do this kind of dance, although I do think about physical problems. How about you, Miyu?
But I don't really know when I'm going to quit. But when I joined MIM, I was 15 or so.
I was 15 or so, and I was the youngest at the time, but then a 13-year-old girl came in. Thirteen? First year of junior high school?
The oldest was 25, but Edo was the same age. People around? Yes, yes, yes. When I see that, I think that I can still do it if I have more seniors.
I think I can do it if I still have senpai.
I think it's a little bit frustrating because that natural cuteness of 13 is a great beautification.
Have you decided? No, I haven't decided. That's why I'm in a bit of a quandary. But he says that everyone who quit thinks it's now. You mean that moment is coming? I don't feel like it's coming at all, and I don't know what I'm going to do.
But when I achieve a goal that I really wanted to achieve, I think, "Oh, it's about time.
I think it's about time.
Please tell me how to get my social networking site to be popular. You two are really strong on social networking sites, aren't you?
TikTok is amazing, isn't it? It's amazing because the other day I had the most followers of any idol on TikTok.
The most followers of any active idol. Wow! 2.2M!
What's that? 1.2 million?
What's 2.2 million? 2.2 million?
What? 100,000?
What? 2.2 million! 2.2 million!
Oh, no!
What? 2.2 million!
But I really don't know why it's so popular... let's see...
What? I mean, the top one is 175,000, right?
Size?
No. 1.75 million?
1,700,000. I don't understand. That's a lot of money. I can't even count it.
Not even if I give it to you at the same time every day?
That's it!
I thought it was a continuation of what I had been doing,
When I was a newcomer, I thought I would do something different from the other members,
For about three years, I gave them ice cream every day.
People thought I was an ice cream girl,
And TikTok.
I would put it up at 7:00 p.m., and people would wait there for me to put it up at 7:00 p.m. So I continued to do that, and thankfully, it got a lot of buzz.
That's important, that's important. It's hard to remember now, and I don't even know what it means anymore.
You have a great creator's spirit.
TikTok is for me.
But YouTube is working too.
I'm going to do what I've decided to do.
If I'm going to put it up every Friday,
I have to do it even if it's last minute.
If I feel like there are people waiting for me, I'll do my best.
I think Instagram is really strong.
I can't do it anymore, but I used to take a selfie every day for 4 or 5 years.
I try to post a lot of selfies on Twitter, and I also think that text is very important.
When I feel like a photo is going to get a lot of attention, I wait for comments with a questioning tone or something.
Long sentences don't grow in popularity, so it's really important to use a single sentence.
I think of a catchphrase with explosive power and post it.
Analytical?
Yes, I do a lot of analysis.
I like to see what's popular right now.
Do you have any MOGI-chan?
I'm really bad at social networking.
I haven't updated my Instagram in over a month.
A month?
Maybe twice this year.
You're going to be removed from Karo's list? I guess so. I'm listening to it now, and I think frequency is important.
Let's just give them a story.
I know it's a story... And really, I'm not good at being traced.
I'm not very good at being traced. But aren't most of the photos that grow in length hard to trace? So...
So it's important to update the site every day before it becomes popular.
Or, if you're going to give advice, you should get some fans to help you out.
Ask your fans to help you.
If you update your stories every day, your fans will be more motivated. Like, "You look cute again today. And then they'll want to go see you again. They want you to become famous, so they make pictures of you and tweet about you with hashtags, so it's another way to get help from your fans.
That's a good idea. It sounds fun right away. So you're going to provide your own material?
I'll do it. I really do. I'll increase the frequency and provide the materials first.I will do it right. Really. I'll also increase the frequency and provide material.
I'm going to implement some of your advice, like not making tweets too long.
I'm glad to hear that. I will do it. Thank you very much.
I'm a stay-at-home mom, so please tell me how to enjoy my time off.
I'm a stay-at-home mom.
When I, for example, have a week or a vacation on short notice,
I stock up on food and never leave the house for a week.
Why?
Do you usually force yourself to go out?
No, I don't have a reason,
I just don't feel the need to go out anymore.
Well, do you want to? Which is it?
I want to go out a lot. I want to go out.
But it depends on the day.
When I have to go out, I go out. If I'm off with no plans, I'll sleep until noon and relax.
If I make plans, I start working in the morning. I am very satisfied with my life, but when I talk about it, I am often told that it is a waste of time and money.
Then, would you have fun if it was worth it? Tell me about it.
But I feel like...
What should I say?
Don't you feel a little guilty when the day ends without doing anything?
Uh...
You feel like you've done nothing today, mij.
So the next time you have a day off, you might try to move around a little.
Ah...
Even if it's just a small thing, like going to the convenience store.
I need to go hit that kind of outside wind one time.
It's like no one knows me.
Heh.
But I'm the type of person who likes to talk, so I might call a friend or something.
If you're at home, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I hate days when we don't talk. Personally.
Oh, man, you don't like anyone today, do you?
You're an idol, right? You're pushing yourself today.
I look at Instagram a lot... and in the search box, there are recommendations for the latest cosmetics.
Like these pants that are popular at GU.
I might go check them out.
Eh?
Oh, I've been thinking about this.
I don't have anything to do today, so I'll go take a look.
I might go there with a feeling of "I don't have anything to do today.
and come back with a purchase.
I see.
You want to go home.
I might want to go home.
Because look at that, it might not be good at all, but it's...
It's amazing that you can get dressed and put on makeup and leave for that.
Well, I don't know what I'm going to do.
My eyes are so deep.
I don't know.
I think it's good that I can have that episode, because if I stay at home all the time, I've already decided what I'm going to do, so I feel like I don't have anything to talk to anyone about today, but I'm going out with my friends or members and deciding on a theme or something.
I'd go out with my friends or other members and decide on a theme and say something like, "Let's do Omorahi today," and then dive into an escape game or something like that.
If you go to a strange café you've never seen before, you might be able to talk about it on stage again someday, somewhere.
You can talk about it on stage again someday.
What was your day like? I'd say, "What was your day like?
I said, "Well, today was really interesting.
I can talk about how I did this and that.
I think that's the advantage of going out.
I feel so good about that now.
So can I ask you to make an omlet ratio for a day with me sometime?
Maybe go to a reptile cafe?
Sounds like fun.
There are so many weird places.
[Question]
You don't remember five years ago.
Like this! Like, "Oh, yeah, that's why.
I know, I know.
Oh, I'm sure Yutan can hear me when I say don't say it.
Maybe...
That was a little too much hand-holding.
I'm sorry.